{
    "subject": "resource/XChange_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Pascale_Bussi\u00e8res",
    "human_readable": "The film XChange features Pascale Bussi\u00e8res.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9124369621276855,
            "question": "What film features Pascale Bussi\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.756638765335083,
            "question": "Has Pascale Bussi\u00e8res won any awards for her role in XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7491622567176819,
            "question": "What other films has Pascale Bussi\u00e8res appeared in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6425231099128723,
            "question": "Who directed the film XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5551977157592773,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5545231699943542,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5132909417152405,
            "question": "Is Pascale Bussi\u00e8res an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48473989963531494,
            "question": "Where was the film XChange filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4709576964378357,
            "question": "Who stars in the film XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41253235936164856,
            "question": "When was the film XChange released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film XChange features Pascale Bussi\u00e8res.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3511_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who stars in the film XChange?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3511_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film XChange filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3511_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Pascale Bussi\u00e8res an actress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3511_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3511_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that supports the triple. The file paths provided point to text files containing articles and reviews, some of which mention Pascale Bussi\u00e8res as an actress or actor in various films and projects, including \"Xchange\". This suggests that she is indeed featured in the film XChange."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information from the documents supports that Pascale Bussi\u00e8res starred in the film \"XChange,\" which is also referred to as \"Xchange\" in some of the texts."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}